I refuse to embrace a victim mentality
because that's not what our grandparents
and Harriet Tubman and those people fought for.
They fought for equal opportunity.
Do not bring up Harriet Tubman's name in vain, baby, please.
Let's say the Lord's name in vain.
Harriet Tubman.
The Lord's name.
Harriet Tubman was literally, literally
saving her family and others from slavery.
Yeah.
You know who helped her?
White people.
They were on the Underground Railroad.
Come on in.
You know who helped her?
No, you know who helped her?
God and Harriet Tubman.
People who benefit from white supremacy.
One of the things that we-
It's a lie.
White supremacy is a lie.
No, sir.
That's simply not true.
It's a lie.
If that were not the case,
then we wouldn't see the continued effort of colonialism
and white people placing themselves in positions of power
when they do not have the power.
You know why they're in positions of power?
Because their culture.
Black culture is toxic.
The black culture is toxic.
We have produced a culture that is toxic.
And let's not-
Let's get on the fact that there's no fathers in the black hole.
Let's get-
Let's talk about that.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Let's talk about that.
None of this is going to work
if y'all are just going to sit here and make up shit.
We have a debate.
It's not going to work.
No, a debate has to be in facts.
You're-
You're putting off emotional liberalism right now.
You're not putting off emotional liberalism.
You're putting off unfounded lies based in conservatism.
That's what y'all do.
Y'all start saying misinformation.
Remember they did the misinformation thing all summer
where everything conservative did.
They said misinformation.
You're carrying a chain around your neck
of an apartheid nation that actively wants to harm
black people and non-Jewish people.
But let me bring it back.
Let me bring it back.